



Dhaka



01998419228



mohd.nazmussa kib@gmail.com



https://github.c om/Meeeeeow

Skiils

Languages & Styling tools: Python, JavaScript, C++, Java HTML, CSS, XML, Typescript, MUI,C#

Frameworks: Bootstrap5, React,

ASP.Net

Backend: Oracle, MSSQL,MySQL

Nazmus Sakib

Career Objective

Have the ability to work under pressure and deliver accordingly. Enthusiast for learning new frameworks or language. Have interest in frontend and full stack development and research works specially NLP and forecasting, pattern recognition-based works.

Education

Monipur High School, Dhaka

Science, GPA of 5.00

Notre dame College, Dhaka

• Science, GPA of 5.00

Ahsanullah University of Science and Technology, Dhaka

Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), CGPA of 3.31(Bachelors)

Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology, Dhaka

Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), July, 2023 – Present (Masters)

Works

Asp.net project (car retail website) semester:3.2
 GitHub link: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/ISD SD 3.2

2. JavaScript & React JS Projects:

GitHub link: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/Mini-Projects-Front-End,

GitHub link(react):

- React redux CRUD: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/react_crud/react-crud
- Wordle: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/redux/react wordle
- E-commerce website with stripe integration: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/cloth e-commerce
- Firebase and store with react:
 https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/authentication_firebase/auth_upload



Rest API works: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react

• From Figma designs: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/marketplace

3. Python Projects

GitHub link: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/Python Projects

Machine learning & NLP: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/machine-learning

4. Typescripts Projects

GitHub link: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/typescript-projects

Experience

Junior Software Developer – Radiant Data systems

Joining date – 1st February,2022 - current Works with oracle, mirth, hl7 data, react, JavaScript. typescript

Part-time Frontend Developer - BiznextIT

Joining date –13th April,2023 – 13th May

Worked with react, typescript, JavaScript, sharetribe marketplace api on an online learning platform

Achievements

 AutoAct: An Auto Labeling Approach Based on Activities of Daily Living in the Wild Domain (10th International Conference on Informatics, Electronics and Vision (ICIEV), 2021

Paper link: https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/9564211

2. Appeared in IELTS - 10 Dec,2022
Reading- 9, Listening- 9, Speaking- 6, Writing- 6

Visit my website: https:/space-raven.netlify.app/

